You need to shred. A shredder is a
wonderful thing because everything that
you think is worthless is of value to
someone else. Here's the problem. You
saw an ad on TV, a guy was stealing a
garbage bag out of a condo, and it told
you to buy the shredder, so you ran down
the store and bought it. The fact is
there are three shredders. There are
straight shredders called ribbon
shredders, and they cut paper straight.
At the FBI lab, we can put back a ribbon
shredder in less than an hour and bring
that bank statement to a federal judge
for an indictment, and we won't miss a
decimal point in the statement. So, that
would be a worthless piece of equipment.
There are some of you go out and buy a
crisscross shredder called the diamond
cut shredder, much better, but we can
put back a document from a diamond cut
shredder in about 8 hours at the lab
like a bank statement and put it back
into court for evidence after it had
been shredded. So, again, you wasted
your money. When you buy a shredder,
since they're all the same price,
obviously buy one that does what you
want it to accomplish, and that is to
destroy whatever it is you're trying to
destroy, and that, of course, is a micro
cut shredder. A micro cut shredder cuts
paper into confetti, so it is absolutely
impossible to put back together. This is
the part I don't understand. You go to
Office Depot, Staples, OfficeMax.
They've taken three shredders, all three
of them, out of a box and put them on
display, and they plugged them in, and
they put a stack of paper there so you
could try them out. So, you went to the
first one, and it cut long strips like
this, and you went to the second one,
and shorter strip, and the other one,
confetti. Which one are you going to
pick? Obviously, the one that's
confetti. If you put a credit card in a
crisscross shredder, the cutter is only
capable of slicing the card in four even
slices. So, if I empty the garbage bag,
take the four slices out, put them on
top of a desk, push them together, I
have everything. Your name, your credit
card number, your expiration date, your
security code, your signature. But, if
you put it in a micro cut shredder, it
turns it into confetti. Every FBI office
in America only uses micro cut
shredders.